The main menu bar includes a number of sub menus,
“开始”菜单栏包含大量的子菜单
on tabs containing the operations and tools that are
标签上包含了特定于你所使用的
particular to the spreadsheet application you are using.
电子表格应用的选项和工具
These are even configurable in Excel as you become more experienced.
当你熟练使用后 甚至可以在 Excel 中重新配置这些菜单
I'm going to go through only a few of these in
我将仅介绍几个 Excel 中的菜单
Excel to give you an idea of what is available.
让你大概了解下都有哪些功能
Google Sheets and Apple Numbers have similar operations to the ones I'm mentioning.
Google 表格和 Apple Numbers 具有和我提到的功能相似的功能
But they may be called something different and they may be found in a different location.
但是叫法和所在的位置可能不同
There are a lot of features available in Excel that you won't find in other spreadsheets.
Excel 中有很多其他电子表格没有的功能
But our intent here is to focus on the features that most spreadsheets have in common.
这门课程的目标是讲解大部分电子表格都具备的功能
The more you work with an application,
使用一款应用的时间越久
the easier its features are to find and use.
就越容易找到和使用应用中的功能
But if you aren't sure, there's always help.
如果不确定 始终可以寻求帮助
Here it is right on the Home menu.
在“开始”菜单的右侧
Type in your search or just click F1.
输入搜索内容或按下 F1
If I'm looking for something I think might be there or just want more information,
如果我想寻找我认为可能存在的功能 或者想了解更多信息
that's where I go first.
我首先会转到这里
File operations are commands that operate between
“文件”菜单是在电子表格
spreadsheets and your computer operating system or online environment.
和计算机操作系统或在线平台之间互相操作的工具
New, we've already used to create a blank spreadsheet but we can also open
我们已经通过“新建”创建了空白电子表格
an existing spreadsheet or use Save As to save a sheet with a new name or format.
我们也可以“打开”现有电子表格 或使用“另存为”将表格另存为新的名称或格式
Edit operations are found in a few different places,
“编辑”功能位于几个不同的位置
but the major ones are in the Home menu.
但主要操作都位于“开始”菜单
Undo and Redo are always visible in the Quick Access Toolbar in the upper left corner,
撤消及恢复按钮 始终在左上角的快速访问工具栏中可见
which is also configurable.
快速访问工具栏也可以配置
The Home menu includes the clipboard functions,
“开始”菜单包含剪贴板功能
Cut, Copy and Paste.
剪切、复制和粘贴
A number of formatting options are also available in the Home menu.
“开始”菜单中还包含一些格式选项
We can set fonts,
可以设置字体
data type and more.
数据类型 等等
There are also shortcuts for table formatting and adding and deleting rows and columns.
还有表格格式 及添加删除行和列的快捷方式
We'll use these features as we need them in the lessons.
我们将在课程需要时 使用这些功能
Formatting your data appropriately,
正确地设置表格格式
helps you document and communicate your analysis.
有助于记录和传达分析结果
This is also where you'll find Search and Replace operations or Find and Select.
你还可以在这里找到查找替换选项 或查找和选择
One tip on this one.
关于这项功能有个提示
Be sure you know the scope of your search or replace.
确保知道搜索或替换的范围
Is it just the selected cell or range,
只是所选单元格
the whole sheet or multiple sheets?
整个工作表还是多个工作表？
This is one of those details that may work
不同电子表格应用在这项功能的
differently on different spreadsheet applications.
细节方面会有所不同
For Excel, a dialog box appears when you
对于 Excel 当你点击“选项”时
click options that you can use to specify the scope.
会出现一个对话框 供你设置范围
Insert menu includes some special items such as hyperlinks.
“插入”菜单包含一些特殊选项 例如超链接
One very important insert function we'll be using a lot is the chart.
我们将经常用到的一个非常重要的插入功能是图表
Creating a chart in spreadsheets is
在电子表格中创建图表是“插入”功能
an Insert operation because the chart will by default,
因为默认情况下
be inserted into the page you're working on.
图表将插入我们正在处理的页面中
We will also cover Pivot Tables in a later lesson.
在后面的课程中 我们还将介绍数据透视表
The Data menu, as you might guess,
你可能已经猜到了 “数据”菜单包含了
includes some important features for data scientists.
一些重要的数据科学功能
These commands allow us to filter our data files,
这些指令使我们能够筛选数据文件
sort lists, and split columns.
对列表排序和拆分列
We'll use these data tools in later lessons.
我们将在后续课程中使用这些数据工具